[With English subtitles]
[有英文字幕]
[Spy Game]
[间谍游戏]
[Episode 7]
[第7集]
Tony.
托尼.
This is B13 sample
这是B13样品
from Jinhai.
from Jinhai.
[Night City]
[夜城]
Have you accomplished your mission?
你完成你的使命了吗？
No.
不。
Why?
为什么？
You know the answer.
你知道答案。
Why are you messing with us?
你为什么要搞砸我们？
screw you?
去你的？
Where did that come from?
那个是从哪里来的？
This is not a game.
这不是一个游戏。
Dr. Feng is your target.
冯医生就是你的目标。
We are your cannon fodder.
我们是你们的炮灰。
you took advantage of us
你利用了我们
steal files
窃取文件
From Dr. Feng's computer.
从冯博士的电脑上。
OK
好的。
you have a nose
你有鼻子
Now an agent.
现在是一名特工。
This is the charm of offline tasks.
这就是离线任务的魅力。
they make you feel
他们会让你感觉
You're really stealing information.
你真的是在偷偷窃取信息。
Without further ado.
废话少说。
This is a real secret theft!
这才是真正的秘密盗窃案！
you deceived us
你欺骗了我们
In the name of gaming.
以游戏的名义。
I quit.
我不干了。
Do you think you can give up?
你觉得你可以放弃吗？
if this wasn't a real game
如果这不是真正的游戏
Do you think you can come and go?
你认为你可以来来去去吗
as you wish?
如你所愿？
Think about it.
想一想。
Since this is
既然这是
real secret theft,
真正的秘密盗窃，
this means
这意味着
you have become
你已经成为
part of an espionage operation.
间谍行动的一部分。
Is it too late for you
对你来说是不是太晚了
Exit the game now?
现在退出游戏吗？
Didn't you find anyone?
你没找到人吗
Uploading files?
正在上传文件？
You are his accomplice.
你是他的同谋。
without your help,
没有你的帮助，
How did the Trojan horse virus in USB come from?
USB中木马病毒是怎么来的
Infect that computer?
感染那台计算机？
You are threatening me.
你在威胁我。
I'm talking about evidence.
我说的是证据。
The game world has rules,
游戏世界有规则，
Although there is a law
虽然有法律
In the real world.
在现实世界。
But what do you ask us to do?
但你要求我们做什么
is illegal.
是非法的。
that's right.
这是正确的。
But you did it anyway.
但你还是这么做了。
We can go to the National Security Bureau
我们可以去国安局
explain the situation
解释情况
and report you.
并把你告发。
Put me in?
把我放进去？
Do you know who I am?
你知道我是谁吗？
you should think about it
你应该考虑一下
how many years
多少年
Accomplices like you two will be sentenced.
像你们两个这样的共犯将会被判刑。
You don't know, right?
你不知道，对吧？
I can tell you.
我可以告诉你。
two defendants
两名被告
Suspected of stealing state secrets
涉嫌窃取国家秘密
By stealing confidential documents.
通过窃取机密文件。
Convicted of espionage.
被判犯有间谍罪。
You are sentenced to six years in prison according to law.
依法判处你有期徒刑六年。
【Please do not make loud noises】
【请勿大声喧哗】
for me,
为我，
There is no loss.
没有损失。
there are many players
有很多玩家
Who can complete the task.
谁能完成任务。
But you two.
但你们两个。
Six years of youth disappeared like this.
六年的青春就这样消失了。
What else can you do after you get out?
出去之后还能做什么？
We don't know anything.
我们什么都不知道。
We're just playing games.
我们只是在玩游戏。
Of course, this is a game.
当然，这是一个游戏。
I always say it's just a game.
我总是说这只是一场游戏。
You are the ones who insist this is a spy game.
你们是那些坚称这是间谍游戏的人。
As long as you keep playing
只要你坚持玩下去
It's always a game,
永远都是一场游戏，
Spy game.
间谍游戏。
Do you have any other questions?
还有其他问题吗？
No.
不。
I said
我说
There are rules in the game.
游戏中有规则。
you must be punished
你必须受到惩罚
Because you have not completed your mission.
因为你没有完成你的使命。
【Resurrection or not】
【复活与否】
Do you believe what they say?
你相信他们说的话吗？
What?
什么？
We broke the law.
我们违反了法律。
I have no idea.
我不知道。
sorry.
对不起。
Why are you apologizing?
你为什么道歉？
There must be something wrong with this game.
这游戏肯定有什么问题。
Apart from,
除了，
They came to me.
他们来找我了。
you?
你？
biological samples
生物样本
and the research of Dr. Feng
以及冯博士的研究
It's all about Bio Group.
一切都与Bio集团有关。
My dad works there.
我爸爸在那里工作。
They framed me.
他们陷害了我。
This has nothing to do with you.
这与你无关。
I'm just playing games.
我只是在玩游戏。
I didn't steal state secrets.
我没有窃取国家机密。
I believe this is a game.
我相信这是一个游戏。
do you still think
你还认为
Is this just a game?
这只是一个游戏？
What...what else could it be?
什……还能是什么？
we just brought
我们刚刚带来了
fake sample
假样品
and try to take some photos
并尝试拍一些照片
from someone's computer.
从某人的计算机。
But in the end we didn't get the photo.
但最终我们还是没有拿到照片。
I won't admit it
我不会承认
I was sinning anyway.
无论如何我都在犯罪。
tell people
告诉人们
at the National Security Agency.
在国家安全局。
Do you think they will believe you?
你认为他们会相信你吗？
why do we have to
为什么我们必须
To the National Security Bureau?
去国安局？
We are only
我们只是
play games.
玩游戏。
sorry.
对不起。
I know something is wrong
我知道出了点问题
With this game.
有了这个游戏。
But what can we do now?
但现在我们能做什么呢？
We can only bury our heads
我们只能埋头
in the sand.
在沙子中。
Do not be afraid.
别害怕。
I did it
我做到了
All on my own.
全靠我自己。
They can't find you.
他们找不到你。
Are you looking down on me?
你是在看不起我吗？
We are partners.
我们是合作伙伴。
if something happens
如果有什么事情发生的话
I won't let you
我不会让你
Bear it alone.
独自承受。
What if I have to go to jail?
如果我必须入狱怎么办？
Will you go with me?
你会和我同去吗？
Can we avoid going to jail?
我们能不去坐牢吗？
do we have
我们是否有
Another option?
另外一个选择？
Yes.
是的。
Keep playing the game.
继续玩游戏。
After we received the 100,000 yuan bonus,
当我们拿到10万元奖金后，
We can leave Jinhai.
我们可以离开金海了。
For this little money?
为了这点钱？
If they really are spies
如果他们真的是间谍的话
They definitely won't let us go.
他们肯定不会放过我们的。
if we have
如果我们有
He did break the law,
确实触犯了法律，
it's too late for us
对我们来说太晚了
Do anything now.
现在就做任何事。
We might as well keep going.
我们不妨继续走下去。
We've come this far.
我们已经走到这一步了。
do you really think
你真的认为
we can do it again
我们可以重来一次
Like in the game?
就像游戏中一样？
Are you not afraid at all?
你一点也不害怕吗？
I am.
我是。
I'm scared
我很害怕
in the game.
在游戏里。
but
但
We were still shot dead by Boss Zhang.
我们还是被张老板枪杀了。
What's the point of being afraid?
害怕有什么意义呢？
But we can't make any more mistakes
但我们不能再犯更多的错误
And getting deeper and deeper!
并且越陷越深！
We can't do this, we can't do this.
我们不能这样做，我们也不能这样做。
Then tell me. What should we do?
那你告诉我。我们应该做什么？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
Anyway,
反正，
We can't play this game anymore.
我们不能再玩这个游戏了。
Regardless, our mission failed.
无论如何，我们的任务失败了。
We can give up.
我们可以放弃了。
No.
不。
We are only
我们只是
play games.
玩游戏。
why do we have to
为什么我们必须
Surrender?
自首？
you sound like
你听起来像
We do sin.
我们确实犯了罪。
Apart from,
除了，
Our debit cards are tied to accounts.
我们的借记卡与账户绑定。
Is it really possible
真的可以吗
What if we quit?
如果我们退出？
forget it. Do what you want to do.
忘了它。做你想做的。
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
I want to be alone for a while.
我想一个人呆一会儿。
[Jinhai Weijing Hotel]
[Jinhai Weijing Hotel]
Your bill, sir.
先生，您的账单。
Thanks.
谢谢。
careful.
小心。
They are checking out and entering the elevator.
他们正在办理退房手续并进入电梯。
Search Shi Lei's home immediately.
立即搜查石磊的家。
[Jinhai Weijing Hotel]
[Jinhai Weijing Hotel]
Hello, is your last phone number 1426?
您好，您最后的电话号码是 1426 吗？
Yes.
是的。
Please fasten your seat belt.
请系好安全带。
We're leaving.
我们要走了。
When we were at the izakaya
我们在居酒屋的时候
I have begun to doubt Shi Lei.
我已经开始怀疑石磊了。
Really?
真的吗？
do you remember
你还记得吗
What shoes does the cleaner wear?
清洁工穿的是什么鞋？
No.
不。
What a coincidence.
真是巧合啊。
that cleaner
那个清洁工
Also wearing a pair of black casual shoes.
还穿着一双黑色休闲鞋。
The cleaner changed in the underground shopping mall
那个清洁工在地下商场换了
and escaped.
并逃脱了。
He can change his shirt.
他可以换衬衫。
He can change hats.
他可以换帽子。
But he doesn’t change shoes on purpose.
但他不会故意换鞋。
Black casual shoes.
黑色休闲鞋。
perhaps
或许
It's just a coincidence.
这只是一个巧合。
Yes.
是的。
So from that moment on,
所以从那一刻起，
I started to calculate
我开始计算
How many coincidences
有多少巧合
It might happen to Shi Lei.
可能会发生在石磊身上。
What's the second coincidence?
第二个巧合是什么？
Shi Lei asked for sick leave
石磊请病假
The day the sample was lost.
样本丢失当天。
This would enable him to commit the crime.
这将使他能够实施犯罪。
Another coincidence.
另一个巧合。
What's the third one?
第三个是什么？
do you remember
你是否记得
That time when Yu Xiaoyue went to get the fake certificate
那个于小月去拿假证书的时候
And she is in danger,
而她正处于危险之中，
Shi Lei appeared?
石磊出现了？
This is another coincidence.
这又是一个巧合。
I doubt Shi Lei
我怀疑石磊
Keep looking at her.
一直在看着她。
Monitoring program on Yu Xiaoyue’s computer
于小月电脑上的监控程序
He also installed it.
也是他安装的。
anything else?
还要别的吗？
Yes.
是的。
Shi Lei is in charge
石磊负责
Welcome Dr. Feng.
欢迎冯博士。
so many coincidences
这么多巧合
Happened to him.
发生在他身上。
This can't be just a coincidence.
这不可能只是巧合。
[Biogenetics Research Report]
【生物遗传学研究报告】
[Researcher, Feng Zixiang]
[Researcher, Feng Zixiang]
[Abstract]
[抽象的]
【Agent Mission】
【代理使命】
【The first way to enter the industry】
【进入业勤第一路】
Sir, let's come to the fourth ring. There is less traffic.
先生，我们来第四环吧。交通量较少。
OK
好的。
15 minutes.
15分钟。
This is enough.
这就够了。
Pull over, right?
靠边停车吧？
Yes.
是的。
How do you pay?
你要怎么付款？
[empty]
[空的]
I'll pay you over the phone.
我会通过电话付钱给你。
OK
好的。
careful.
小心。
[Vanke, Tianyu Phase II]
【万科，天域二期】
[All programs]
[所有节目]
Verification successful.
验证成功。
[Su Yanxiu]
[Su Yanxiu]
This is just part of it.
这只是其中的一部分。
Why?
为什么？
I ask for more from this.
我对此要求更多。
You are blackmailing me.
你这是在敲诈我。
At least you have to give me a reason.
至少你要给我一个理由。
Because of this game,
因为这场比赛，
i lost myself
我迷失了自己
with my girlfriend.
和我的女朋友。
Isn't this enough?
这还不够吗？
No one forces you to do this.
没有人强迫你这样做。
you need money
你需要钱
Come support your girlfriend.
来支持你的女朋友。
We need you to get the data.
我们需要你来获取数据。
We each get what we need.
我们各取所需。
certainly,
当然，
I'm deeply sorry
我深感抱歉
For what happened to you.
对于发生在你身上的事情。
But you don't have to be sad
但你不必悲伤
For girls like her.
对于像她这样的女孩。
Whether it's necessary or not
不管有没有必要
This is my own business.
这是我自己的事。
you just need to consider
你只需要考虑
Whether you accept my offer or not.
不管你是否接受我的提议。
How much do you want?
你想要多少？
1 million yuan.
100万元。
use cash.
用现金。
With this offer,
有了这个优惠，
we will not
我们不会
Let’s cooperate again
再合作吧
Then I won't do it.
那我就不干了。
You broke the rules.
你违反了规则。
Rules are made by those with bargaining leverage.
规则是由有谈判筹码的人制定的。
I know
我知道
Dr. Feng studies the value of data.
冯博士研究数据的价值。
if you don't want
如果你不想要的话
I can always find someone else.
我总能找到别人。
Do you think
你认为
You can negotiate with me
你可以和我协商
Only half the information?
只有一半的信息？
If you get caught by the NSA,
如果你被国家安全局抓到，
Depending on what you do,
根据你所做的事情，
you will end up just
你最终只会
worse than Yu Xiaoyue.
worse than Yu Xiaoyue.
You don't want me to get caught, do you?
你不想让我被抓住吧？
Boss Zhang.
张老板。
after all,
毕竟，
We have been in contact outside of the game as well.
我们在比赛之外也有过接触。
Outside the game?
游戏之外？
he may know
他可能知道
Boss Zhang’s true identity.
张老板的真实身份。
one million.
一百万。
You can think about it one day.
你有一天可以考虑一下。
Shi Lei and Boss Zhang had a falling out.
石磊和张老板闹翻了。
He might have planned it
他或许早就计划好了
To fight against the night fog.
去对抗夜雾。
Do you think Boss Zhang will agree to his proposal?
你觉得张老板会同意他的提议吗？
It depends on how much he knows.
这取决于他知道多少。
This is an opportunity to find Boss Zhang.
这是一个找到张老板的机会。
Do you think Boss Zhang is in Jinhai?
你以为张老板在金海？
Think about it.
想一想。
Shi Lei wants one million yuan in cash
石磊要一百万元现金
in one day.
一天内。
Boss Zhang
张老板
No objection was raised.
没有提出异议。
This means it is very likely
这意味着很有可能
I know she is in Jinhai.
知道她在金海。
He knows your true identity, right?
他知道了你的真实身份，对吗？
He was just bluffing.
他只是虚张声势。
efficient.
有效。
Shi Lei is smarter than I thought.
石磊比我想象的要聪明。
He always wants to go out.
他总是想出去。
We can't keep people like him.
我们留不住他这样的人。
Our superiors have agreed
我们的上级已经同意了
with our plans.
与我们的计划。
Since the night fog
自从夜雾之后
Already worked very hard
已经很努力了
to win Huang Zicheng over,
to win Huang Zicheng over,
future,
将来，
they will arrange
他们会安排
Offline tasks are more important to him.
对他来说更重要的线下任务。
We still need to get Huang Zicheng
我们还需要得到黄子成
to cooperate
要合作
with our task force.
与我们的特别工作组。
However, Huang Zicheng
However, Huang Zicheng
Never received professional training.
从未接受过专业培训。
his mission is
他的使命是
Provide us with offline game information
向我们提供线下游戏信息
Help us
帮助我们
Uncover the deployment of spy games in Gimhae.
揭开间谍游戏在金海的部署。
We need to give him more guidance.
我们需要给他更多的指导。
knew.
知道了。
where are we going?
我们去哪？
You'll know when we get there.
当我们到达那里你就会知道。
brother.
兄弟。
I just have one question. only one.
我只有一个问题。只有一个。
Will I go to jail?
我会进监狱吗？
Can you give me a straight answer?
你能给我一个直接的答案吗？
I can't give you a verdict.
我无法给你一个判决。
but now,
但现在，
You must correct your attitude.
你必须端正你的态度。
This is no longer a game.
这不再是一场游戏。
This is a battle.
这是一场战斗。
Chief Gao.
高科长.
Go in, I'll wait for you outside.
进去吧，我在外面等你。
hurry up.
赶快。
We invite you here today
我们今天邀请你来这里
There are several questions.
有几个问题。
understand?
理解？
Yes.
是的。
What should I say to you?
我该向你说什么？
Wu Xi.
吴熙.
This is a secret location.
这是一个秘密地点。
You should be mentally prepared, right?
你应该有心理准备吧？
Actually I'm not
其实我不是
Be mentally prepared.
做好心理准备。
Anyway, we have to start.
无论如何，我们必须开始。
what have you done
你做了什么
After you go back?
你回去之后？
After I go back,
我回去之后，
I just submitted the task.
我刚刚提交了任务。
and then?
进而？
Then I asked her
然后我问她
If she uses us to steal secrets.
如果她利用我们窃取秘密。
She didn't answer me directly.
她没有直接回答我。
She just said it was just a game,
她只是说这只是一个游戏，
if it is really
如果真的是
perform espionage missions,
执行间谍任务，
We have broken the law.
我们已经触犯了法律。
We would go to jail for this.
我们会因此入狱。
actually i know
其实我知道
she is threatening me
她在威胁我
Lest I call the police.
以免我报警。
I always wanted to expose her true self.
我一直想暴露她的真实自我
Face to face for long periods of time.
长时间面对面。
But I held back.
但我忍住了。
after that,
在那之后，
She kills us.
她杀了我们。
Did she kill you?
她杀了你？
Yes.
是的。
We didn't get the job done.
我们没有完成任务。
That's a punishment.
那是一种惩罚。
damn it.
该死的。
if i didn't meet you
如果我没有遇见你
in advance,
提前，
I would be really scared by them
我真的会被他们吓到
And let them manipulate me.
并让他们操纵我。
Aren't you scared now?
你现在不害怕了吗？
I am.
我是。
I'm worried you'll arrest me
我担心你会逮捕我
And put me in jail.
并把我关进监狱。
if you really are
如果你真的是
Put me in jail
要把我关进监狱
I would feel so wronged.
我会觉得好委屈。
Aren't you afraid of Boss Zhang?
你就不怕张老板吗？
No.
不。
She only knows how to hide in the virtual world.
她只知道躲在虚拟世界里。
If we really quarrel
如果我们真的吵架了
In the world of agents,
在特工世界里，
Not sure who will survive.
不确定谁能幸存。
do you still think
你还认为
Is this just a game?
这只是一个游戏？
if i tell you
如果我告诉你
Those who caught you in Bangkok
那些在曼谷抓到你的人
It's a spy,
是间谍，
Will you still be as calm as you are at this moment?
你还会像此时此刻一样平静吗？
But we are in Jinhai.
但我们在金海。
I don't think they dare.
我想他们不敢。
I do not think so.
我不这么认为。
you know what happened
你知道发生了什么
Is it also available in Bangkok?
曼谷也有吗？
time has not come yet
时间未到
For your questions.
供您提问。
I forgot.
我忘了。
when you go back,
当你回去的时候，
have you ever mentioned it to anyone else
你有没有向其他人提到过
Our meeting?
我们的会议？
No, what should I do?
不，我该怎么做？
What's Yaoyao's reaction?
瑶瑶什么反应
after her
在她之后
Did you discover the truth?
发现真相了吗？
she...
她...
She was just shocked and scared.
她只是感到震惊和害怕。
like
就像
my first reaction
我第一次的反应
Found this out.
发现了这件事。
Does she show this tendency?
她有表现出这种倾向吗
Does she want to keep playing the game?
她想继续玩这个游戏吗？
She also thinks there's something wrong with the game.
她也觉得这个游戏有问题。
But there is nothing we can do.
但我们无能为力。
No one wants to go to jail, right?
没有人愿意进监狱，对吧？
this means
这意味着
She wanted to keep playing the game.
她想继续玩这个游戏。
No, it's not like that.
不，不是那样的。
How are you two doing?
你们两个怎么样
Know each other?
知道对方？
we have met
我们见过面
through this game.
通过这个游戏。
She returned to Jinhai from Los Angeles.
她从洛杉矶回到金海。
This is a first for both of us
这对我们俩来说都是第一次
Perform offline tasks.
执行离线任务。
That's all what happened in Bangkok.
这就是曼谷发生的全部事情。
I think you know it all.
我想你都知道了。
do you know
你知道吗
Why is she playing this game?
她为什么玩这个游戏？
She just thinks this game is fun.
她只是觉得这个游戏很好玩。
But she cares about the prize.
但她很在乎奖金。
In fact, I am also very concerned about this.
其实我也很关心这个。
Who wouldn't be excited to see a bonus of 100,000 yuan?
看到十万元的奖金谁会不兴奋呢？
except her,
除了她之外，
Do you have any other partners?
你还有其他合作伙伴吗？
I have
我有
a teammate
一个队友
called Jiang Xiaohua.
called Jiang Xiaohua.
She's playing the game too.
她也在玩这个游戏。
Is this her real name?
这是她的真名吗？
Yes.
是的。
Please help me write it down.
请帮我写下来。
[Jiang Xiaohua]
[Jiang Xiaohua]
when will she start
她什么时候开始
Play this game?
玩这个游戏？
A few months ahead of me.
比我早几个月。
Her game is higher than mine.
她的游戏水平比我高。
She also has more connections than I do.
她也比我有更多的联系。
has she ever
她有没有过
Have you done offline tasks before?
以前做过离线任务吗？
Offline mission?
离线任务？
she may not have
她可能还没有
Complete any offline tasks.
完成任何离线任务。
If she does any offline tasks,
如果她做了任何线下任务，
She would definitely tell me.
她肯定会告诉我。
Jiang Xiaohua
Jiang Xiaohua
Definitely clean.
绝对是干净的。
We will investigate this.
我们将对此进行调查。
how much do you know
你知道多少
Where is Boss Zhang?
张老板呢？
Boss Zhang.
张老板。
Boss Zhang’s role in the game
张老板在游戏中的角色
It's a woman.
是一个女人。
I have no idea
我不知道
What she looks like in real life.
她在现实生活中的样子。
but by talking to her
但通过与她交谈
In the game,
在游戏里，
I think
我认为
She might actually be a woman.
她可能真的是个女人。
Why?
为什么？
Because she is more sensitive,
因为她比较敏感，
And she spoke at a very steady pace.
而且她说话的语速很稳定。
she has a subordinate
她有一个下属
His character is a soldier.
其角色是一名士兵。
He doesn’t talk much, but he’s a badass.
他话不多，但他是个坏蛋。
he is that person
他就是那个人
Who kills us in the game.
谁在游戏中杀了我们。
His level is level 50.
他的等级是50级。
when you are
当你是
play this game,
玩这个游戏，
have you ever doubted
你有没有怀疑过
What is the purpose of this game?
这个游戏的目的是什么？
No.
不。
I just think this game
我只是觉得这个游戏
marvelous.
太棒了。
It's so lifelike.
真是栩栩如生。
It's just like
就像是
I'm really an agent
我真的是经纪人
and completely immersed in it
并完全沉浸其中
In the world of agents.
在代理人的世界里。
These are not excuses.
这些都不是借口。
according to
根据
Information we have
我们掌握的信息
And your confession,
还有你的告白，
You are now working for a spy.
你现在正在为间谍工作。
Well, you can't blame that on me.
好吧，你不能把这归咎于我。
I'm a victim too.
我也是受害者。
if i knew there was
如果我知道有
The spy organization behind this game,
这个游戏背后的间谍组织，
I won't
我不会
Did those things.
做过那些事。
But the fact is that you have
但事实是你已经
Committed secret theft.
犯下了秘密盗窃罪。
if you were a spy
如果你是间谍
and you want to use the game
并且您想使用该游戏
Use this as an excuse to get out of jail,
以此为借口出狱，
no one can prove
没有人能证明
You didn't mean it.
你不是故意的。
when i first knew
当我第一次知道
They're using me,
他们在利用我，
I want it immediately
我立刻想要
Catch the person behind it.
抓住背后的人。
It was you who stopped me.
是你阻止了我。
I could have caught him.
我本可以抓住他的。
Then it's our fault
那么就是我们的错
Do you work for a spy?
你为间谍工作？
Of course, I was wrong. I admit.
当然，我错了。我承认。
but you
但是你
You should have your own plans, right?
你应该有自己的打算吧？
This must be your plan
这一定是你的计划
You didn't catch the guy.
你没有抓住那个人。
you stopped me
你阻止了我
Because you don't want me to mess up your plans.
因为你不想让我打乱你的计划。
Officer Wu, am I right?
吴警官，我说得对吗？
if you
如果你
Targeted me a long time ago
很久以前就瞄准了我
then you should know
那么你应该知道
I'm just a gamer.
我只是一个游戏玩家。
we won't arrest you
我们不会逮捕你
This doesn't mean you are clean.
这并不意味着你是干净的。
we have a plan
我们有计划
When are we going to arrest you, do you understand?
我们什么时候要逮捕你，明白吗？
Am I in big trouble?
我有大麻烦了吗？
If not, why are you here?
如果不是，你为什么会在这里？
Is there any way out for me?
我还有退路吗？
It's up to you.
这取决于你。
So I have.
所以我有。
tell me. what should I do?
告诉我。我应该怎么办？
According to the current situation,
根据目前的情况，
If you cooperate with our investigation,
如果您配合我们的调查，
we can give it to you
我们可以给你
Lesser penalties.
较轻的处罚。
Ha...what should I do?
哈……怎么办？
keep playing games
继续玩游戏
and accept offline tasks.
并接受离线任务。
If Boss Zhang contacts you,
如果张老板联系你，
Report it to us immediately.
立即向我们报告。
in other words,
换句话说，
Do you want me to be your informant?
你想让我做你的线人吗？
To be precise,
准确地说，
It's to help us solve the case.
是为了帮助我们破案。
Where is my partner?
我的伙伴呢？
Can my partner?
我的伙伴可以吗
help you
帮你
The case was also solved?
案子也破了？
knew.
知道了。
You only want me.
你只想要我。
You think too much.
你想多了。
Mind your own business first.
先管好自己的事吧。
We meet here today...
今天我们在这里见面...
I won't tell anyone.
我不会告诉任何人。
no way.
绝不。
So you agreed?
所以你同意了？
What choice do I have?
我还有什么选择？
I'm not saying no.
我并不是说不。
only
只是
A lot happened today.
今天发生了很多事情。
I need to go back and figure it out.
我需要回去弄清楚。
This is a huge responsibility. I can't be in such a hurry.
这是一个巨大的责任。我不能这么急。
no problem. Take it easy.
没问题。慢慢来。
But don't take too long.
但不要花太长时间。
contact me
联络我
When you make up your mind.
当你下定决心的时候。
I remembered your phone number.
我记住了你的电话号码。
You can get your business card back.
您可以拿回您的名片。
I have a habit of deleting messages after reading them.
我有读完消息后就删除的习惯。
Director Qin, how are you?
秦处长，怎么样？
He responded quickly.
他反应很快。
He showed no obvious signs
他没有表现出明显的迹象
nervous
紧张
or fear.
或恐惧。
Through my observation,
通过我的观察，
Huang Zicheng has some potential.
Huang Zicheng has some potential.
This is also
这也是
one of the reasons
原因之一
Why he stands out in the agent race.
为什么他在经纪人比赛中脱颖而出。
let's go. I'll walk you home.
我们走吧。我送你回家。
Don't you have anything to say to me?
你就没有什么话要对我说吗？
Think about what you can do.
想想你能做什么。
If you want to continue,
如果你想继续，
You have to be mentally prepared.
你必须做好心理准备。
This is no longer a game.
这不再是一场游戏。
This is risky.
这是有风险的。
Stop letting people kill you.
别再让别人杀了你。
do not scare me.
别吓我。
if i were a real agent
如果我是真正的经纪人
I won't be worse than you.
我不会比你差。
So why does it need more time?
那为什么还需要更多时间呢？
My partner.
我的合伙人。
She is also a victim.
她也是受害者。
I can't leave her alone.
我不能丢下她不管。
I have to get her settled.
我得让她安定下来。
Don't be so naive.
别这么天真。
Which offline player
哪个离线玩家
in game
在游戏里
Simple?
简单吗？
No, did you just say,
不，你刚才是不是说，
Or do you really think there is something wrong with Yaoyao?
还是你真的觉得瑶瑶有什么问题？
Did you persuade her to quit the game?
你劝她退出游戏了吗？
I guess she won't give up.
我猜她不会放弃。
Really?
真的吗？
If there's really something wrong with her
如果她真的有什么问题的话
she should
她应该
Keep playing,
继续玩，
correct?
正确的？
do not you know
你不知道吗
Is the world of agents a good place?
特工的世界好不好？
everyone there
那里的每个人
There are many different faces.
有许多不同的面孔。
It's not easy to explain
这并不容易说清楚
Who is the big bad wolf or the little rabbit.
谁是大灰狼还是小兔子。
let's go.
我们走吧。
open the door. let's go.
打开门。我们走吧。
[Biodiversity Day]
[生物多样性日]
[inbox]
[收件箱]
[Boss Zhang: Give me some time to raise money. 】
【张老板：给我点时间筹钱。】
[OK]
[好的]
Shi Lei.
Shi Lei.
The seminar is about to begin.
研讨会即将开始。
future.
未来。
[Man and nature are connected and complement each other]
【人与自然相连、相辅相成】
[Biomedical Research]
[生物医学研究]
turn around.
回转。
OK
好的。
Now we are basically sure
现在我们基本确定
That Shi Lei
那个石磊
It's Ace Agent,
是王牌特工，
"professor."
“教授。”
He also negotiated with Boss Zhang,
他还和张老板谈判，
hope to receive
希望收到
The agent was compensated 1 million yuan.
特务赔偿100万元。
Do they agree?
他们同意吗？
Yes.
是的。
1 million yuan
100万元
Not a small amount.
不是一个小数目。
should we try
我们应该尝试吗
Contact bank
联系银行
Check
查看
which customer
哪个客户
Withdrawal made?
已提款？
So, we can analyze them one by one.
所以，我们可以一一分析。
spy
间谍
Always cautious.
总是很谨慎。
He couldn't withdraw all the money at once.
他不可能一下子把钱全部取出来。
The scope of this clue
该线索的范围
Too broad.
太宽泛了。
Hard to check.
很难检查。
The most effective thing to do right now
现在最有效的事情
Just pay attention to Shi Lei
就是关注石磊
Found that Boss Zhang was following him.
发现张老板跟着他。
I will send two more teams
我会再派出两支队伍
Support you.
支持你。
We need 24-hour monitoring.
我们需要24小时监控。
knew.
知道了。
OK
好的。
[fish leaping]
[鱼跃]
Shi Lei and Yu Xiaoyue
Shi Lei and Yu Xiaoyue
Both loved this restaurant.
两人都非常喜欢这家餐厅。
Not only them,
不仅是他们，
And Han Jie.
还有韩杰。
This boss Zhang
这位张老板
I will definitely contact Shi Lei again.
一定会再次联系石磊的。
If there's really something wrong with her
如果她真的有什么问题的话
She would definitely expose herself.
她肯定会暴露自己。
Let's wait and see.
让我们等着看。
Jiahui is back.
Jiahui is back.
boss.
老板。
Arrange flowers.
布置鲜花。
Take it to the kitchen.
把它带到厨房。
OK
好的。
Boss Zhang has already contacted Shi Lei.
张老板已经联系上了石磊。
Put her through.
让她接通。
Hello?
你好？
The money is ready
钱已经准备好了
and was placed in the old place.
并被放置在旧的地方。
I need some time back.
我需要一些时间回来。
Shi Lei left.
Shi Lei left.
Did you finish it?
你做完了吗？
Yeah, put it on my label.
是的，把它放在我的标签上。
OK
好的。
goodbye.
再见。
careful.
小心。
[fish leaping]
[鱼跃]
At least the person who called him
至少给他打电话的人
Not Jiahui.
不是嘉慧。
Follow him.
跟着他。
[Building 5]
[5号楼]
[No. 45 Ventilation room]
[不。45 通风机房]
[exit]
[出口]
Luggage has been stored
行李箱已寄存
half an hour ago.
半小时以前。
that's a man
那是一个男人
A man wearing a black shirt stores it.
穿着一件黑色衬衫的人存放着它。
any follow up
任何后续行动
About this person's whereabouts?
关于这个人的下落？
After leaving the compound,
离开大院后，
He disappeared into the blind spot of surveillance.
他消失在监视的盲点里。
We can't find that man
我们找不到那个男人的
Follow-up whereabouts.
后续行踪。
Could this person be Boss Zhang?
难道这个人就是张老板？
Hello?
你好？
Have you received the money?
你收到钱了吗？
What's the password?
密码是什么？
Send me the file.
把文件发给我。
Give me your password first.
先把密码给我吧。
I need to see the money first.
我需要先看到钱。
Sixty-four.
六四。
wrong password.
密码错误。
Are you bleeding?
你在流血吗？
You've played a trick on me!
你玩弄我了！
clam down.
冷静下来。
Send me the other half of the file,
把文件的另一半发给我，
I'll tell you the real password.
我会告诉你真正的密码。
I can pry open the box
我可以撬开箱子
No code!
没有代码！
Not only do you need money,
你不仅需要钱，
But you also need to detox.
但你也需要排毒。
Boss Zhang
张老板
Never wanted to make a deal with him.
从来不想和他做交易。
He was poisoned.
他中毒了。
Liu, get off the car!
刘，下车！
[Su Yanxiu]
[Su Yanxiu]
I'll send it to you.
我将其发送给你。
I'll send it to you now.
我现在就发给你。
[Electric vehicles and bicycles are prohibited from passing]
【电动车、自行车禁止通行】
walk the stair.
走楼梯。
I sent it. What's the password?
我寄了。密码是什么？
password is
密码是
Your game registration date.
您的游戏注册日期。
think about it
考虑一下
A souvenir.
一个纪念品。
Where is the money?
钱在哪里？
Detox. Detox.
排毒。排毒。
you lied to me!
你骗了我！
Shi Lei!
Shi Lei!
Shi Lei! Shi Lei!
Shi Lei! Shi Lei!
hurry!
匆忙！
Shi Lei, wake up!
Shi Lei, wake up!
Shi Lei! Shi Lei! Shi Lei!
Shi Lei! Shi Lei! Shi Lei!
help me!
帮我！
Boss Zhang is in Jinhai.
Boss Zhang is in Jinhai.
Call an ambulance!
打电话叫救护车！